[{"answer": "She created a kind of prison that she couldn't get out of.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "And what does Michelle think Marilyn's life was really like?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well, I want -- let's just say I was well.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "-- of something that was done on -- something done on this new fangled technology thing called Tout.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "I don't understand what issue you have with that.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "You see?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Well, precisely for the reasons that that video has just shown me, which is that I should -- the further I am away from Meredith Vieira, the better for my career.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "What is that about?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, yes, I would.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "But I realized then -- I realized it, and I mean this in all sincerity, actually, that you were a -- at heart I saw a brilliant journalist and that's as I suspect how you would like to be seen, isn't it?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's really weird, Piers, because when I left the \"Today\" show that was my decision.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "What's it been like for you?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "5:00.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Why did you have to get up at 2:30 in the morning because you didn't have to be there until about 5:30?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Well, I have to be careful because I am part of \"Rock Center\" as well.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Do you feel liberated to have an opinion?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Is it Barack Obama being weak as president?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Well, I think you would get different answers to that.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Or is there something just fundamentally inherently wrong the process now that has to be dramatically changed?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Well, I would think that people are truly fed up at this point and they're frustrated and they're hurting because of the economy as well.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "People that watch the \"Today\" show who lead an often this very normal live well away from all this who must be looking at this in complete -- I would imagine -- increasingly indignant bemusement saying what is happening here to the people supposedly charged with making our lives better?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "It was hard that day.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "What were your emotions like?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Well, I've had it for almost 40 years.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "What has it been like for you battling most of your adult life knowing that you have this awful condition?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think you deal with it on a day-to-day basis.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Is it very difficult?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Well, look, it's a -- it's a long road.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "How have you managed to stay as you appear to be pretty cheery about life?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Well, we knew that at some point we were going to have to open up to them and tell them the truth.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "When did you decide to tell the children that you had multiple sclerosis and how did they react to it?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Not nearly enough.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Well, we're told that they are no more susceptible than the general population, maybe slightly more susceptible.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Do you know whether they are susceptible to getting this?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "They couldn't have a better role model than their father?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "I love it.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Do you just enjoy it?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "You tell me.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "For all these people who are desperate to be a millionaire, what's it like?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Well, people get in for all sorts of reasons.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "As somebody who has worked her way up the journalistic ladder, and done it the hard way and with great integrity and so on, how do you feel about the appointment of Chelsea Clinton as an NBC reporter, given that whatever her connections, whatever her background, she clearly hasn't done the journalistic hard yards?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "I would -- boy, I've seen a lot of places and I've done a lot of things.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Of all the amazing moments you've experienced as a journalist, Meredith, in your career, if you could relive one again in the next five minutes, if I had that power, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "She's sitting next to me.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "What's been the love of a great woman like Meredith in life for you and your life particularly, given the challenges that you've had to face?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Because I've always loved Michelle's work.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Why Michelle Williams?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I think there's a lot of ingredients in that decision, if you like.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "What is the decision making process as a filmmaker in choosing the right kind of person to play somebody so famous?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Oh, gosh, I suppose the sort of -- the biggest discovery that I made along the way was that Marilyn Monroe was a character, and that how we commonly think of her, that was a part that she played.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "What surprised you most about her?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "You're just looking for the right man.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "How did that happen?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Oh, gosh, I don't know.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Do you feel a bit weird when you watch it back there, just how convincing it is?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "I suppose that was one of my other big discoveries along the way, is that, more than anything, she wanted to be a serious actress.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "ORGAN: Michelle, what did you think of Marilyn as an actress?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "So I think after the break, Simon I want to know whether Michelle Williams is equally as big a diva?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "No, I think that's a very good description.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Anything else you want to tell us about her?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "ILLIAMS: In al honesty, I run ten minutes late every day, everywhere.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Are you like that, or are you very professional about these things?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Honestly, no.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "I mean, admit it, Michelle, you must feel sexy when you're playing Marilyn Monroe?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "You know, it -- I've never spent this long with a character before.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "Why did you find it so emotional?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "It has a routine.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "How is life for you?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Very, very excited.", "docId": "111121pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "In your big directing debut, you must be excited?", "qSentId": 651}]